indiancinemagallery.com 2019-02-25

# Privacy Policy - Indian Cinema Gallery

Privacy Policy of **www.indiancinemagallery.com**

This Website collects some Personal Data from its Users.

### Data Controller and Owner

Indiancinemagallery.com  
Rainoh Entertainments,  
Karunagappally  
Kollam, Kerala  
Phone : +91 9745755562

_**indiancinemagallery@gmail.com**_

### Types of Data collected

Among the types of Personal Data that this Website collects, by itself or through third parties, there are: Cookie, Usage Data, First Name and Email.

Other Personal Data collected may be described in other sections of this privacy policy or by dedicated explanation text contextually with the Data collection.  
The Personal Data may be freely provided by the User, or collected automatically when using this Website.  
Any use of Cookies – or of other tracking tools – by this Website or by the owners of third party services used by this Website, unless stated otherwise, serves to identify Users and remember their preferences, for the sole purpose of providing the service required by the User.  
Failure to provide certain Personal Data may make it impossible for this Website to provide its services.

The User assumes responsibility for the Personal Data of third parties published or shared through this Website and declares to have the right to communicate or broadcast them, thus relieving the Data Controller of all responsibility.

### Mode and place of processing the Data

### Methods of processing

The Data Controller processes the Data of Users in a proper manner and shall take appropriate security measures to prevent unauthorized access, disclosure, modification, or unauthorized destruction of the Data.  
The Data processing is carried out using computers and/or IT enabled tools, following organizational procedures and modes strictly related to the purposes indicated. In addition to the Data Controller, in some cases, the Data may be accessible to certain types of persons in charge, involved with the operation of the site (administration, sales, marketing, legal, system administration) or external parties (such as third party technical service providers, mail carriers, hosting providers, IT companies, communications agencies) appointed, if necessary, as Data Processors by the Owner. The updated list of these parties may be requested from the Data Controller at any time.

### Place

The Data is processed at the Data Controller’s operating offices and in any other places where the parties involved with the processing are located. For further information, please contact the Data Controller.

### Retention time

The Data is kept for the time necessary to provide the service requested by the User, or stated by the purposes outlined in this document, and the User can always request that the Data Controller suspend or remove the data.

### The use of the collected Data

The Data concerning the User is collected to allow the Website to provide its services, as well as for the following purposes: Advertising, Analytics, Contacting the User, Content commenting, Displaying content from external platforms and Interaction with external social networks and platforms.

The Personal Data used for each purpose is outlined in the specific sections of this document

### Detailed information on the processing of Personal Data

Personal Data is collected for the following purposes and using the following services:

### Advertising

These services allow User Data to be utilized for advertising communication purposes displayed in the form of banners and other advertisements on this Website, possibly based on User interests.  
This does not mean that all Personal Data are used for this purpose. Information and conditions of use are shown below.  
Some of the services listed below may use Cookies to identify Users or they may use the behavioral retargeting technique, i.e. displaying ads tailored to the User’s interests and behavior, including those detected outside this Website. For more information, please check the privacy policies of the relevant services.

#### Google AdSense (Google)

Google AdSense is an advertising service provided by Google Inc. This service uses the “Doubleclick” Cookie, which tracks use of this Website and User behavior concerning ads, products and services offered.  
Users may decide to disable all the Doubleclick Cookies by clicking on: **[google.com/settings/ads/onweb/optout?hl=en](http://www.google.com/settings/ads/onweb/optout?hl=en).**

You may also opt out of a third-party vendor’s use of cookies for interest based advertising by visiting **[aboutads.info](http://www.aboutads.info/)**

Personal Data collected: Cookie and Usage Data.

Place of processing : USA – **[Privacy Policy](http://google.com/privacy/ads/)**

### Analytics

The services contained in this section enable the Owner to monitor and analyze web traffic and can be used to keep track of User behavior.

#### Display Advertising extension for Google Analytics (Google)

Google Analytics on this Website might use Google’s Interest-based advertising, 3rd-party audience data and information from the DoubleClick Cookie to extend analytics with demographics, interests and ads interaction data.

Personal Data collected: Cookie and Usage Data.

Place of processing : USA – **[Privacy Policy](http://www.google.com/intl/en/policies/privacy/)** – **[Opt Out](http://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout?hl=en)**

#### Google Analytics (Google)

Google Analytics is a web analysis service provided by Google Inc. (“Google”). Google utilizes the Data collected to track and examine the use of this Website, to prepare reports on its activities and share them with other Google services.  
Google may use the Data collected to contextualize and personalize the ads of its own advertising network.

Personal Data collected: Cookie and Usage Data.

Place of processing : USA – **[Privacy Policy](http://www.google.com/intl/en/policies/privacy/)** – **[Opt Out](http://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout?hl=en)**

#### Google Tag Manager (Google)

Google Tag Manager is an analytics service provided by Google, Inc.

Personal Data collected: Cookie and Usage Data.

Place of processing : USA – **[Privacy Policy](http://www.google.com/intl/en/policies/privacy/)**

#### Histats (Wisecode)

Histats is an analytics service provided by Wisecode S.r.l.

Personal Data collected: Cookie and Usage Data.

Place of processing : Italy – **[Privacy Policy](http://www.histats.com/?act=5)**

### Displaying content from external platforms

These services allow you to view content hosted on external platforms directly from the pages of this Website and interact with them.  
If a service of this kind is installed, it may still collect web traffic data for the pages where the service is installed, even when users do not use it.

#### Youtube video widget (Google)

Youtube is a video content visualization service provided by Google Inc. that allows this Website to incorporate content of this kind on its pages.

Personal Data collected: Cookie and Usage Data.

Place of processing : USA – **[Privacy Policy](http://www.google.it/intl/en/policies/privacy/)**

### Content commenting

Content commenting services allow Users to make and publish their comments on the contents of this Website.  
Depending on the settings chosen by the Owner, Users may also leave anonymous comments. If there is an email address among the Personal Data provided by the User, it may be used to send notifications of comments on the same content. Users are responsible for the content of their own comments.  
If a content commenting service provided by third parties is installed, it may still collect web traffic data for the pages where the comment service is installed, even when users do not use the content commenting service.

#### Facebook Comments (Facebook)

Facebook Comments is a content commenting service provided by Facebook Inc. enabling the User to leave comments and share them on the Facebook platform.

Personal Data collected: Cookie and Usage Data.

Place of processing : USA – **[Privacy Policy](http://www.facebook.com/privacy/explanation.php)**

### Interaction with external social networks and platforms

These services allow interaction with social networks or other external platforms directly from the pages of this Website.  
The interaction and information obtained by this Website are always subject to the User’s privacy settings for each social network.  
If a service enabling interaction with social networks is installed it may still collect traffic data for the pages where the service is installed, even when Users do not use it.

#### Facebook Like button and social widgets (Facebook)

The Facebook Like button and social widgets are services allowing interaction with the Facebook social network provided by Facebook Inc.

Personal Data collected: Cookie and Usage Data.

Place of processing : USA – **[Privacy Policy](http://www.facebook.com/privacy/explanation.php)**

#### Google+ +1 button and social widgets (Google)

The Google+ +1 button and social widgets are services allowing interaction with the Google+ social network provided by Google Inc.

Personal Data collected: Cookie and Usage Data.

Place of processing : USA – **[Privacy Policy](http://www.google.com/intl/en/policies/privacy/)**

#### Pinterest “Pin it” button and social widgets (Pinterest)

The Pinterest “Pin it” button and social widgets are services allowing interaction with the Pinterest platform provided by Pinterest Inc.

Personal Data collected: Cookie and Usage Data.

Place of processing : USA – **[Privacy Policy](http://about.pinterest.com/privacy/)**

#### ShareThis (Sharethis Inc.)

ShareThis is a service provided by ShareThis Inc., which displays a widget that allows interaction with social networks and external platforms as well as sharing the contents of this Website.  
Depending on the configuration, this service can display widgets belonging to third parties such as the managers of social networks where interactions are shared. In this case, also the third parties that provide the widget will be informed of interactions and Usage Data on the pages where this service is installed.

Personal Data collected: Cookie and Usage Data.

Place of processing : USA – **[Privacy Policy](http://sharethis.com/privacy)**

#### Twitter Tweet button and social widgets (Twitter)

The Twitter Tweet button and social widgets are services allowing interaction with the Twitter social network provided by Twitter Inc.

Personal Data collected: Cookie and Usage Data.

Place of processing : USA – [Privacy Policy](http://twitter.com/privacy)

### Further information about Personal Data

### Age eligibility and children privacy

Users declare to be adult according to their applicable legislation. Minors may use this Website only with the assistance of a parent or guardian. Under no circumstance persons under the age of 13 may use this Website.

### Additional information about Data collection and processing

### Legal action

The User’s Personal Data may be used for legal purposes by the Data Controller, in Court or in the stages leading to possible legal action arising from improper use of this Website or the related services.  
The User is aware of the fact that the Data Controller may be required to reveal personal data upon request of public authorities.

### Additional information about User’s Personal Data

In addition to the information contained in this privacy policy, this Website may provide the User with additional and contextual information concerning particular services or the collection and processing of Personal Data upon request.

### System Logs and Maintenance

For operation and maintenance purposes, this Website and any third party services may collect files that record interaction with this Website (System Logs) or use for this purpose other Personal Data (such as IP Address).

### Information not contained in this policy

More details concerning the collection or processing of Personal Data may be requested from the Data Controller at any time. Please see the contact information at the beginning of this document.

### The rights of Users

Users have the right, at any time, to know whether their Personal Data has been stored and can consult the Data Controller to learn about their contents and origin, to verify their accuracy or to ask for them to be supplemented, cancelled, updated or corrected, or for their transformation into anonymous format or to block any data held in violation of the law, as well as to oppose their treatment for any and all legitimate reasons. Requests should be sent to the Data Controller at the contact information set out above.

This Website does not support “Do Not Track” requests.  
To determine whether any of the third party services it uses honor the “Do Not Track” requests, please read their privacy policies.

### Changes to this privacy policy

The Data Controller reserves the right to make changes to this privacy policy at any time by giving notice to its Users on this page. It is strongly recommended to check this page often, referring to the date of the last modification listed at the bottom. If a User objects to any of the changes to the Policy, the User must cease using this Website and can request that the Data Controller erase the Personal Data. Unless stated otherwise, the then-current privacy policy applies to all Personal Data the Data Controller has about Users.

### Information about this privacy policy

### Definitions and legal references

#### Personal Data (or Data)

Any information regarding a natural person, a legal person, an institution or an association, which is, or can be, identified, even indirectly, by reference to any other information, including a personal identification number.

#### Usage Data

Information collected automatically from this Website (or third party services employed in this Website ), which can include: the IP addresses or domain names of the computers utilized by the Users who use this Website, the URI addresses (Uniform Resource Identifier), the time of the request, the method utilized to submit the request to the server, the size of the file received in response, the numerical code indicating the status of the server’s answer (successful outcome, error, etc.), the country of origin, the features of the browser and the operating system utilized by the User, the various time details per visit (e.g., the time spent on each page within the Website) and the details about the path followed within the Website with special reference to the sequence of pages visited, and other parameters about the device operating system and/or the User’s IT environment.

#### User

The individual using this Website, which must coincide with or be authorized by the Data Subject, to whom the Personal Data refer.

#### Data Subject

The legal or natural person to whom the Personal Data refers to.

#### Data Processor (or Data Supervisor)

The natural person, legal person, public administration or any other body, association or organization authorized by the Data Controller to process the Personal Data in compliance with this privacy policy.

#### Data Controller (or Owner)

The natural person, legal person, public administration or any other body, association or organization with the right, also jointly with another Data Controller, to make decisions regarding the purposes, and the methods of processing of Personal Data and the means used, including the security measures concerning the operation and use of this Website. The Data Controller, unless otherwise specified, is the Owner of this Website.

#### This Website

The hardware or software tool by which the Personal Data of the User is collected.

#### Cookie

Small piece of data stored in the User’s device.

* * *

#### Legal information

Notice to European Users: this privacy statement has been prepared in fulfillment of the obligations under Art. 10 of EC Directive n. 95/46/EC, and under the provisions of Directive 2002/58/EC, as revised by Directive 2009/136/EC, on the subject of Cookies.

This privacy policy relates solely to the Website (www.indiancinemagallery.com)

Latest update: October 16, 2014

**Children’s Information**  
We believe it is important to provide added protection for children online. We encourage parents and guardians to spend time online with their children to observe, participate in and/or monitor and guide their online activity. http://www.indiancinemagallery.com does not knowingly collect any personally identifiable information from children under the age of 13. If a parent or guardian believes that http://www.indiancinemagallery.com has in its database the personally-identifiable information of a child under the age of 13, please contact us immediately (using the contact in the first paragraph) and we will use our best efforts to promptly remove such information from our records.

**Online Privacy Policy Only**  
This privacy policy applies only to our online activities and is valid for visitors to our website and regarding information shared and/or collected there. This policy does not apply to any information collected offline or via channels other than this website.

**Consent**  
By using our website, you hereby consent to our privacy policy and agree to its terms.

**Update**  
This Privacy Policy was last updated on: Friday, June 29th, 2017.  
_Should we update, amend or make any changes to our privacy policy, those changes will be posted here_
